jumpboygame.com 2016-12-10

# Privacy Policy - jumpboygame Games Online

This privacy policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use information about our visitors. Flashcricketgames.com does not target its games and services to ages under 13, but we do our best to protect those under 13. 

**What information we collect**

To enhance the user experience and prevent abuse, we collect not-personal informaion such as IP. Our website also utilize a standard technology called cookies and webserver logs to collect informaion about how our website is used.Sometime our ad providers (EpicGameAds and Google Adsense) may also use cookies which allow them to place ads on our website. When you visit our site ad companies may collect information such as ip address and clickstream information.

We only collect information which is necessary. We do not collect any personal information like phone number, address etc unless you are willing to provide them through registraion. 

**Sharing Information with Third Parties**

We will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public. 

**Your Consent**

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by FlashCricketGames.com If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us using our "contact us" form. 

Log-in to save favourites
